To move from one activity. In this case,
the MainActivity in our sunshine app, to another, here
the DetailActivity, we call StartActivity. But note that when
using the StartActivity method, rather than specifying the class
name of the activity to start directly, that
class name is packaged explicitly within an intent. The
basic premise is simple. Whenever you need your app
components to communicate with each other, or the system,
you use intents to identify the
target destination. Starting activities within your
app is the simplest example. [SOUND]
With your intent explicitly indicating the target
using the context and a class name of the activity. Intents that use the
name of the component you're targeting directly, are known as explicit intents.